Hudson River Sloop Clearwater, Inc. Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 2. Publications, 2; 4.5 Linear Feet Boxes: 41 - 47 Folders: 1127 - 1341
  - Subseries 2.4: Department of Environmental Conservation (DEC) Regulations, 2.4; 0.75 Linear Feet Boxes: 42 - 43 Folders: 1190 - 1208
    - Report of the Fixed Station Conventional Parameter Water Quality Surveillance Network 1986 (Folder 1206, Box 43)
    - Report of the Fixed Station Toxics Surveillance Network 1984 (Folder 1207, Box 43)
    - Toxic Chemical Reduction Draft, Aug. 1993 (Folder 1208, Box 43)
  - Subseries 2.5: Superfund, 2.5; 0.25 Linear Feet Box: 43 Folders: 1209 - 1232
    Series contains publications by Superfund concerning environmental issues
    - Actions Needed to Correct Long-Standing Contract Management Problems (Folder 1209, Box 43)
    - CERCLA/ SARA 1987 (Folder 1210, Box 43)
    - Coming Clean: Superfund Problems Can Be Solved (Folder 1211, Box 43)
    - Compendium of Superfund Program Publications (Folder 1212, Box 43)
    - Correspondence (Folder 1213, Box 43)
    - Environmental Progress (Folder 1214, Box 43)
    - EPA Cost Estimates are not Reliable or Timely (Folder 1215, Box 43)
    - Exposure Assessment Manuel (Folder 1216, Box 43)
    - Hudson Falls Superfund Site 1989 Amendment to 1986 C.O. (Folder 1217, Box 43)
    - Hudson Falls Superfund Site 1986 Consent Order (Folder 1218, Box 43)
    - Hudson Falls Superfund Site Chronology (Folder 1219, Box 43)
    - Laws and Regulations (legal size) (Folder 1220, Box 43)
    - Legislative Matters (Folder 1221, Box 43)
    - Massena, NY Superfund Site (Folder 1222, Box 43)
    - Massena, NY Superfund Site Reports (Folder 1223, Box 43)
    - Missed Statutory Deadlines Slow Progress in Environmental Programs (Folder 1224, Box 43)
    - A More Vigorous and Better Managed Enforcement Program is Needed (Folder 1225, Box 43)
    - New York State Superfund Info (Folder 1226, Box 43)
    - No Time to Lose: A critical Overview of the Super Slow State Superfund with Recommendations for Reform (Folder 1227, Box 43)
    - Problems with the Completeness and Consistency of Site Cleanup Plans (Folder 1228, Box 43)
    - Risk Assessment Process and Issues (Folder 1229, Box 43)
    - Strategy Summary (Folder 1230, Box 43)
    - The Superfund Innovative Technology Evaluation Program (Folder 1231, Box 43)
    - Waukegan Harbor (Folder 1232, Box 43)
  - Subseries 2.6: State Environmental Quality Review Act (SEQRA) Regualtions, 2.6; 0.5 Linear Feet Box: 44 Folders: 1233 - 1240
    Series contains pamphlets outlining SEQRA Regulations
    - Ad Hoc SEQRA Committee (Folder 1233, Box 44)
    - Comments on Revisions (Folder 1234, Box 44)
    - Correspondence and Notes for Revision (Folder 1235, Box 44)
    - Meetings on Revisions (Folder 1236, Box 44)
    - Orange County Scoping Meeting (Folder 1237, Box 44)
    - Revisions 1994 (Folder 1238, Box 44)
    - Scope on Revisions (Folder 1239, Box 44)
    - State Environmental Quality Review (Folder 1240, Box 44)
  - Subseries 2.7: Printed Materials, 1977 - 1990; 2.7; 0.5 Linear Feet Box: 44 Folders: 1241 - 1275
    Series contains various printed materials, including pamphlets, Clearwater Navigator, and others Hudson River Valley
    - Advance Treatment Technologies for Disposal of Hazardous Waste (Folder 1241, Box 45)
    - Appeals Procedure (legal size) (Folder 1242, Box 45)
    - California Standards (Folder 1243, Box 45)
    - Clearwater Navigator 1982 (Folder 1244, Box 45)
    - Clearwater Navigator 1985 (Folder 1245, Box 45)
    - Clearwater Navigator 1986 (Folder 1246, Box 45)
    - Clearwater Navigator 1989 (Folder 1247, Box 45)
    - Clearwater Navigator 1990 (Folder 1248, Box 45)
    - Coastal Erosion (Folder 1249, Box 45)
    - The Conservationist, July-Aug. 1977 (Folder 1250, Box 45)
    - Deciding Critical Water Issues in a Time of Austerity: Directions for the Decade (Folder 1251, Box 45)
    - Docking Catalogues (Folder 1252, Box 45)
    - Docks and Marina Information: Construction, Engineering (Folder 1253, Box 45)
    - Fisheries in Sweden (Folder 1254, Box 45)
    - Flood Plan Handouts (Folder 1255, Box 45)
    - Health Advisories 1993 (Folder 1256, Box 45)
    - Information Leaflet: Some Marine Algae of New York State (Folder 1257, Box 45)
    - Island Press Environmental Sourcebook (Folder 1258, Box 45)
    - Let’s All Help the Harbor (Folder 1259, Box 45)
    - Modern Water Trails: A Guide to Establishing and Maintaining Recreational Waterways (Folder 1260, Box 45)
    - Navigator/Articles - Ideas (Folder 1261, Box 45)
    - New York State DEC Central and Regional Office Telephone Directory 1992 (Folder 1262, Box 45)
    - Pamphlet: 1982 Guide to Angling for Hudson River Shad (Folder 1263, Box 45)
    - Pamphlet: Clearwater’s Great Hudson River Revival 1991 (Folder 1264, Box 45)
    - Pamphlet: Proposed Regulations for Striped Bass Management in New York (Folder 1265, Box 45)
    - Presentation: CVS Visual Aid (Folder 1266, Box 45)
    - Proposal Striped Bass Regulations 1987 (Folder 1267, Box 45)
    - Riverlovers, Inc. (Folder 1268, Box 45)
    - Scenic Designations (Folder 1269, Box 45)
    - The Sediment Solution (Folder 1270, Box 45)
    - The Sierra Club Guide to Radio News Feeding (Folder 1271, Box 45)
    - Sports Illustrated (Folder 1272, Box 45)
    - The Tidal Exchange (Folder 1273, Box 45)
    - Tracing a River’s Toxic Pollution (Folder 1274, Box 45)
    - World Resources Institute (Folder 1275, Box 45)
  - Subseries 2.8: Reports and Studies, 2.8; 1.5 Linear Feet Boxes: 45 - 47 Folders: 1276 - 1341
    Series contains various reports and studies concerning environmental action in and around the Hudson River Valley
    - 1988 EPA SARA Info. Form R Reporting Regs, List of Lists (Folder 1276, Box 45)
    - 1997 Year-Class Report for the Hudson River Monitoring Program (Folder 1277, Box 45)
    - Bard College Draft Environmental Impact Statement (Folder 1278, Box 45)
    - CA Striped Bass Studies, 1980 (Folder 1279, Box 45)
    - Chemicals in Sportfish and Game (Folder 1280, Box 45)
    - Comments on the Proposed Recommendations for Striped Bass Management in New York Waters (Folder 1281, Box 45)
    - Draft Framework for Watershed-Based Trading (Folder 1282, Box 45)
    - Environmental Impact Statement on the Hudson River PCB Reclamation Demonstration Project - Draft, May 1981 (Folder 1283, Box 45)
    - EPA 1994 Toxics Release Inventory (Folder 1284, Box 45)
    - EPA 1994 Toxics Release Inventory State Fact Sheet (Folder 1285, Box 45)
    - Evaluation of the New York State Hazardous Waste Site Remediation Program (Folder 1286, Box 45)
    - Final Environmental Impact Statement for Policy on Contaminants in Fish (Folder 1287, Box 45)
    - Final Environmental Impact Statement for Revisions/Enhancements to... Solid Waste Management Facilities (Folder 1288, Box 45)
    - Freshwater Wetlands: Delineation Manual (Folder 1289, Box 45)
    - Freshwater Wetlands Permit Requirements, Regulations, and Revisions (Folder 1290, Box 45)
    - Global Marine Biological Diversity (Folder 1291, Box 45)
    - Guidance for Conducting Remedial Investigations and Feasibility Studies under Cercla (Folder 1292, Box 45)
    - Heushnet River Estuary: Addendum to Draft Feasibility Study of Remedial Action Alternatives (Folder 1293, Box 45)
    - Hudson Falls Consent Order 7/15/1993 (Folder 1294, Box 45)
    - The Hudson River Almanac 1994-1995 Vol. 1, No. 1 (Folder 1295, Box 45)
    - Hudson River Estuary Boating Access Needs and Opportunities Plan and General Environmental Impact Statement (Folder 1296, Box 45)
    - Hudson River Estuary Management Program Annual Report and State of the Hudson Report 4/12/1996-3/31/1997 (Folder 1297, Box 45)
    - Hudson River Estuary Management Program Annual Report and State of the Hudson Report 4/1/1997-3/31/1998 (Folder 1298, Box 45)
    - Hudson River Foundation (Folder 1299, Box 45)
    - Hudson River Habitat Restoration: Hudson River Basin, New York Reconnaissance Report (Folder 1300, Box 45)
    - The Incidence and Severity of Sediment Contamination in Surface (Folder 1301, Box 46)
    - The Incidence and Severity of Sediment Contamination in Surface Waters of the U.S. Vol. 2: Data Summaries for Areas of Probable Concerns (Folder 1302, Box 46)
    - The Incidence and Severity of Sediment Contamination in Surface Waters of the U.S. Vol. 3: National Sediment Contaminant Point Source Inventory (Folder 1303, Box 46)
    - Interim Characterization and Evaluation for the Hudson River PCB Reassessment (Folder 1304, Box 46)
    - Investigations of Cancer Incidence near 38 Landfills with Soil Gas Migration Conditions: New York State, 1980-1989 (Folder 1305, Box 46)
    - The Journal of Industrial Hygiene “Possible Systemic Effects from Certain Chlorinated Hydrocarbons” Sept. 1937 (legal size) (Folder 1306, Box 46)
    - Living on the Edge: Urban Waterfront Edges with Aquatic Habitats (Folder 1307, Box 46)
    - Mid-Hudson Site Study Phase I: Needs Analysis (Folder 1308, Box 46)
    - Montgomery Place Environmental Studies (Folder 1309, Box 46)
    - Multi-Media Pollution Prevention in New York State 1993-1994 Annual Report (Folder 1310, Box 46)
    - Municipal Sewage Sludge Management Practices in New York State (Folder 1311, Box 46)
    - National Study of Chemical Residue in Fish, Vol. 2 (Folder 1312, Box 46)
    - New York Harbor Water Quality Survey: Executive Summary 1994 (Folder 1313, Box 46)
    - New York-New Jersey Harbor: Effects on Birds (Folder 1314, Box 46)
    - New York-New Jersey Harbor: Pollutant Loadings (Folder 1315, Box 46)
    - New York-New Jersey Harbor: Toxic Categoration (Folder 1316, Box 46)
    - New York-New Jersey Harbor: Toxic Characterization (Folder 1317, Box 46)
    - New York Assembly Oversight Report: DEC May 15, 1998 (Folder 1318, Box 46)
    - New York Assembly Oversight Report: DEC June 18, 1998 (Folder 1319, Box 46)
    - New York State Hazardous Waste Facility Siting Plan (Folder 1320, Box 46)
    - New York State Performance Partnership Agreement - State Fiscal Year 1996-1997 (Folder 1321, Box 46)
    - Northeastern Environmental Science (Folder 1322, Box 46)
    - Partitioning Behavior of Polychlorinated Biphenyls (Folder 1323, Box 46)
    - A Plan for Pier 84 (Folder 1324, Box 46)
    - Platforms for Growth (Folder 1325, Box 46)
    - Profit from Pollution Prevention (Folder 1326, Box 46)
    - The Quality of Our Nation’s Waters: Nutrients and Pesticides (Folder 1327, Box 47)
    - Reassessment of Liver Findings in Five PCB Rat Studies IEHR-1991 (Folder 1328, Box 47)
    - Reports and Publications from Hudson River Foundation-Sponsored Research (Folder 1329, Box 47)
    - Revisions/Enhancements to New York State’s Solid Waste Management Facilities (Folder 1330, Box 47)
    - Risk Assessment Guidance for Superfund, Vol. 1: Human Health Evaluation Manual (Folder 1331, Box 47)
    - Risk Assessment Guidance for Superfund, Vol. 2: Environmental Evaluation Manual (Folder 1332, Box 47)
    - Seafood Safety (Folder 1333, Box 47)
    - Significant Coastal Fish and Wildlife Habitats Program (Folder 1334, Box 47)
    - Striped Bass Regulations 1987 (Folder 1335, Box 47)
    - Striped Bass Report and 1985 Decision (Folder 1336, Box 47)
    - Striped Bass Stock Assessment in Rhode Island Waters 1981-1982 (Folder 1337, Box 47)
    - Striped Bass Task Force Report to the Governor (Folder 1338, Box 47)
    - Uniform Procedures and Regulations (Folder 1339, Box 47)
    - Waste Management Research Report: Focus on Marine Population (Folder 1340, Box 47)
    - Wastes in Marine Environments Summary (Folder 1341, Box 47)
- 3. Office papers, 3; 1.5 Linear Feet Boxes: 47 - 48 Folders: 1342 - 1410
  Series contains subseries consisting of correspondence, documents concerning legislation, and various office materials
  - Subseries 3.1: Legislation, 3.1; 0.5 Linear Feet Box: 47 Folders: 1342 - 1353
    Series contains correspondence concerning New York State Legislation and political impact on the environment.
    - 1994 Legislation (Folder 1342, Box 47)
    - Coalition for Effective Government 1992-1993 (Folder 1343, Box 47)
    - Environmental Congress 1991 (Folder 1344, Box 47)
    - Environmental Infrastructure Funding (Folder 1345, Box 47)
    - Environmental Program 10/1992 (Folder 1346, Box 47)
    - Governmental Reform 1992-1993 (Folder 1347, Box 47)
    - Legislation 1992 (Folder 1348, Box 47)
    - Legislature 1992 (Folder 1349, Box 47)
    - Legislation Notes (Folder 1350, Box 47)
    - New York State Legislation: TRI for Gov. Agencies - Gov. (Folder 1351, Box 47)
    - Pataki: Election Materials (Folder 1352, Box 47)
    - Peter Lanahan Environmental Board 6/1992 (Folder 1353, Box 47)
  - Subseries 3.2: Committees, 1984 - 1991; 3.2; 0.5 Linear Feet Boxes: 47 - 48 Folders: 1354 - 1378
    Series contains minutes of various committees in which Clearwater participated.
    Alphabetical, Chronological
    - DEC Marina Advisory Committee (Folder 1354, Box 47)
    - Environmental Action Committee (Folder 1355, Box 47)
    - Estuary Management 1993 (Folder 1356, Box 47)
    - Hudson River Estuary Management Committee (legal size) (Folder 1357, Box 47)
    - Hudson River Estuary Management Program (Folder 1358, Box 47)
    - Hudson River Estuary Management Program - Legal/Regulatory Issues (Folder 1359, Box 47)
    - Hudson River Estuary Quarterly Issues Update and State of the Hudson Report (Folder 1360, Box 47)
    - Hudson River Estuary Regulatory Study (Folder 1361, Box 47)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Advisory Committee 1984 (Folder 1362, Box 48)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Advisory Committee 1985 (Folder 1363, Box 48)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Advisory Committee 1986 (Folder 1364, Box 48)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Management Advisory Committee 1987 (Folder 1365, Box 48)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Advisory Committee - Annual Report to the Commissioner and the Legislature (Folder 1366, Box 48)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Advisory Committee: Mailing Labels (Folder 1367, Box 48)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Advisory Committee Meeting Notes - John Mylod (legal size) (Folder 1368, Box 48)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Advisory Committee - Meeting Notices and Notes (Folder 1369, Box 48)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Advisory Committee Meetings 1987 (Folder 1370, Box 48)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Advisory Committee, Program Report 1981-1982 (Folder 1371, Box 48)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Advisory Committee - Reports (Folder 1372, Box 48)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Management Committee (Folder 1373, Box 48)
    - Political Action Committee Spending 1992 Election (Folder 1374, Box 48)
    - Poughkeepsie Waterfront Advisory Committee Meetings (Folder 1375, Box 48)
    - Region 3 Open Space Advisory Committee (Folder 1376, Box 48)
    - Waterfront Advisory Committee (Folder 1377, Box 48)
    - Waterfront Advisory Committee Membership (Folder 1378, Box 48)
  - Subseries 3.3: Correspondence, 3.3; 0.2 Linear Feet Box: 48 Folders: 1379 - 1386
    Series contains Communication between Clearwater and various people and organizations
    - Correspondence (Folder 1379, Box 48)
    - Correspondence: John Mylod (Folder 1380, Box 48)
    - Correspondence: Rep. Sue Kelly 1995 (Folder 1381, Box 48)
    - Major Projects Correspondence (Folder 1382, Box 48)
    - New Administration Crap (Correspondence) (Folder 1383, Box 48)
    - Office Letterhead (Folder 1384, Box 48)
    - Pat Yazzi (Folder 1385, Box 48)
    - War (1991) (Folder 1386, Box 48)
  - Subseries 3.4: Events, 3.4; 0.1 Linear Feet Box: 14 Folders: 1387 - 1395
    Publications and communication about events hosted by Clearwater
    - Arm of the Sea Players (Folder 1387, Box 48)
    - Arm of the Sea Players Grant Proposal (Folder 1388, Box 48)
    - Clearwater 1992 Revival - Ben and Jerry’s Support (Folder 1389, Box 48)
    - Planner Workshop Originals (Folder 1390, Box 48)
    - Poughkeepsie Tricentennial (Folder 1391, Box 48)
    - Pumpkin Sail (Folder 1392, Box 48)
    - Revival (Folder 1393, Box 48)
    - Sloop Clubs (Folder 1394, Box 48)
    - Sloop Clubs Organizing 1995 (Folder 1395, Box 48)
  - Subseries 3.5: Office Paperwork, 3.5; 0.1 Linear Feet Box: 48 Folders: 1396 - 1405
    Secretarial paperwork concerning employee benefits and Clearwater bi-laws
    - 403(b) - Metlife (Folder 1396, Box 48)
    - Activist Network (Folder 1397, Box 48)
    - Activist Network Forms (Folder 1398, Box 48)
    - Bi-Laws (Folder 1399, Box 48)
    - Clearwater Auto Regulations (Folder 1400, Box 48)
    - Computer Networks (Folder 1401, Box 48)
    - Form R Information (Folder 1402, Box 48)
    - Interns (Folder 1403, Box 48)
    - Neva River Project (Folder 1404, Box 48)
    - Project Budgets (Folder 1405, Box 48)
  - Subseries 3.6: Ligitation, 3.6; 0.1 Linear Feet Box: 48 Folders: 1406 - 1410
    Lawsuits against Clearwater
    - Clearwater vs. HRPC (Folder 1406, Box 48)
    - Comments on the Proposed Recommendations for Striped Bass Management in New York Waters (Folder 1407, Box 48)
    - Litigation Clearwater vs. Navy Admin: 1985 Steering Committee (Folder 1408, Box 48)
    - Litigation: Project Sponsor Group (Folder 1409, Box 48)
    - Robbins vs. Clearwater 1990 (Folder 1410, Box 48)
- 4. John Mylod’s Projects and Interests, 1981 - 1995; 4; 4 Linear Feet Boxes: 49 - 53 Folders: 1411 - 1653
  Documents collected by John Mylod, President of Clearwater, Inc., of his interests in environmental action
  - 1995 Budget (Folder 1411, Box 49)
  - ACOE Hudson River Restoration Project (Folder 1412, Box 49)
  - ACOE New York State PGP (Folder 1413, Box 49)
  - Alaska Oil Spill (Folder 1414, Box 49)
  - Albany/Rensselaer - Potential Docking Areas (Folder 1415, Box 49)
  - Alsen Coal Lawsuit: Update (Folder 1416, Box 49)
  - Alsen Coal Terminal (Folder 1417, Box 49)
  - Background for Discussion of Limited Entry Fisheries (Folder 1418, Box 49)
  - Bay of Fundy - Effect of Turbidity... and Relationship to Local Fisheries (Folder 1419, Box 49)
  - Bay of Fundy - Tidal Power (Folder 1420, Box 49)
  - Between the Railroad and the River; The Hudson River Access Forum, Sept. 1989 (Folder 1421, Box 49)
  - The Big Picture (Folder 1422, Box 49)
  - Boat/Yacht Club Associations (Folder 1423, Box 49)
  - Brief for Petitioners - Applicants RE: Board of Education Pine Plains Central School District (Folder 1424, Box 49)
  - A Brief Report on PCB in Hudson River Striped Bass, 1992 (Folder 1425, Box 49)
  - A Brief Report of PBC in Hudson River Striped Bass, July 1994 (Folder 1426, Box 49)
  - Bureau of Fisheries Continuous Executive Program Plan (Folder 1427, Box 49)
  - Burncolor Reports (Folder 1428, Box 49)
  - Calendar of Events (Folder 1429, Box 49)
  - Catch and Release: Upper Hudson, 1995 (Folder 1430, Box 49)
  - Chelsea, 1993 (Folder 1431, Box 49)
  - Chelsea Pump Station, Spring 1994 (Folder 1432, Box 49)
  - Cibro Gasoline Corporation and Cibro Petroleum Products, Inc. (Folder 1433, Box 49)
  - Clearwater Alaska Fund (Folder 1434, Box 49)
  - Clearwater Sch. 1986 (Folder 1435, Box 49)
  - Coal Plants (Folder 1436, Box 49)
  - Coalition for a Lead-Free New York (Folder 1437, Box 49)
  - Coastal Resource Management Program Outline (Folder 1438, Box 49)
  - Comments Regarding Proposed Amendments: 6NYCRR Parts 624 and 622 (Folder 1439, Box 49)
  - Commercial Fishery Policy (Folder 1440, Box 49)
  - Commissioner’s Response to Fisheries Committee 1986 (Folder 1441, Box 49)
  - COMNET (Folder 1442, Box 49)
  - The Conservationist (Folder 1443, Box 49)
  - Constitution Island Marsh (Folder 1444, Box 49)
  - Court-Related Needs of the Elderly and Persons with Disabilities (Folder 1445, Box 49)
  - Coyeman’s Landfill, Jan. 1995 (Folder 1446, Box 49)
  - Creating a Special Place: A Plan to Preserve the Hudson River and Erie Canal Corridors (Folder 1447, Box 49)
  - David’s Island (Folder 1448, Box 49)
  - Davies Place (Folder 1449, Box 49)
  - DEC Comparative Risk Project, 1995 (Folder 1450, Box 49)
  - DEC Water Quality Enhancement and Protection Policy (Folder 1451, Box 49)
  - Development and Management of Hudson Estuary Fish Resources (Folder 1452, Box 49)
  - Docking (Folder 1453, Box 49)
  - Docking Catalogues (Folder 1454, Box 49)
  - Dollar Savers Rebate Program (Folder 1455, Box 49)
  - DOS Sail Beacon, Sept. 1992 (Folder 1456, Box 49)
  - Dovel Manag./Computer (Folder 1457, Box 49)
  - Draft Environmental Impact Statement Scoping Meeting (Folder 1458, Box 49)
  - Draft Fishery Management Plan, Revised 6/9/85: Shad et al (Folder 1459, Box 49)
  - Dutchess City Ash Landfill (Folder 1460, Box 49)
  - Energy 1993 (Folder 1461, Box 50)
  - Engle vs. Pulver (Folder 1462, Box 50)
  - Environment vs. Jobs (Folder 1463, Box 50)
  - Environmental Action, 1994 (Folder 1464, Box 50)
  - Environmental Action Program: Current Priorities, 1993 (Folder 1465, Box 50)
  - Environmental Action Survey - Rensselaer (Folder 1466, Box 50)
  - Environmental Advocates (Folder 1467, Box 50)
  - Environmental Associate I - Shoreline Specialist (Folder 1468, Box 50)
  - Environmental Associate II (Folder 1469, Box 50)
  - Environmental Associates - Former Personnel (Folder 1470, Box 50)
  - Environmental Benefit Permit Strategy II (Folder 1471, Box 50)
  - Environmental Communication (Folder 1472, Box 50)
  - Environmental Concerns of Real Estate and Business Transactions (Folder 1473, Box 50)
  - Environmental Liaison Group, Jan. 1995 (Folder 1474, Box 50)
  - Environmental Planning (Folder 1475, Box 50)
  - EPL/Boyle (Folder 1476, Box 50)
  - EPL Conflict of Interest (Folder 1477, Box 50)
  - EPL Jorling Issue (Folder 1478, Box 50)
  - Environmental Quality Awards (Folder 1479, Box 50)
  - Esopus Meadows Environmental Center (Folder 1480, Box 50)
  - Evolution of the Hudson Estuary Fisheries Development Program by William Doval (Folder 1481, Box 50)
  - Forms First - Saratoga Landfills (Folder 1482, Box 50)
  - Ferry Sloops Docking/Home (Folder 1483, Box 50)
  - Final Report on the Development and Evaluation of a System for Rating Fish and Wildlife (Folder 1484, Box 50)
  - Fish Advisory Project (Folder 1485, Box 50)
  - Fish - Dovel (Folder 1486, Box 50)
  - Fort Wadsworth 1981 (Folder 1487, Box 50)
  - General Support (Folder 1488, Box 50)
  - Green Island (Folder 1489, Box 50)
  - Green Island Incinerator (Folder 1490, Box 50)
  - Greenpeace (Folder 1491, Box 50)
  - Greenway (Folder 1492, Box 50)
  - Greenway Memorandum (Folder 1493, Box 50)
  - Greenway, July 1992 (Folder 1494, Box 50)
  - Halfmoon in Beacon? (Folder 1495, Box 50)
  - Harriman Sewage Treatment Plant (Folder 1496, Box 50)
  - Hazardous Waste, 1991 (Folder 1497, Box 50)
  - HRIF Grants (Folder 1498, Box 50)
  - Hudson-Athens Lighthouse Preservation Society: Grant Proposal (Folder 1499, Box 50)
  - Hudson Estuary Fisheries Development Program First Annual Report, 1980/1981 (Folder 1500, Box 50)
  - Hudson Estuary Fisheries Development Program Progress Report for the Fiscal Year 1981-1982 (Folder 1501, Box 50)
  - Hudson Estuary Program Progress Report for 1982-1984 (Folder 1502, Box 50)
  - Hudson Falls - Citizen Participation Plan (Folder 1503, Box 50)
  - Hudson Fisheries Task Force Hinchy Proceedings (Folder 1504, Box 50)
  - Hudson Recycling, Inc. (Folder 1505, Box 50)
  - Hudson River Angler Captured LMB, 1985 (Folder 1506, Box 50)
  - Hudson River Esplanade Park (Folder 1507, Box 50)
  - Hudson River Estuary Bill (Folder 1508, Box 50)
  - Hudson River Estuary Fishery Management Program 1985-1986 Annual Report (Folder 1509, Box 50)
  - Hudson River Estuary Fishery Management Program 1985-1986 Progress Report (Folder 1510, Box 50)
  - Hudson River Estuary Program Implementation 9/8/87 (Folder 1511, Box 50)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association and DEC Correspondence on Memorandum of Understanding, 1987 (Folder 1512, Box 50)
  - Hudson River Fishery Management Law, 1980 (Folder 1513, Box 50)